[Music]  this attitude you have right now is the  reason nobody likes you  you think you're cooler than everybody  just because your glasses are square for  some reason  and you're vegetarian but i've got news  for you  those things don't make you cool in fact  they make you look really [ __ ] gay  do i look like i give a [ __ ] what you  think about me cyrus i have always been  alone ever since the day my mommy and  daddy were brutally slaughtered right in  front of me in cold blood  [Music]  you're not the only one with a dark past  trevor  we all have problems  but most of us don't go around acting  like winey babies  and bully others because of our  insecurities you remember what happened  to my dad  he was turned into a robot or some [ __ ]  by dr robotnik and became a weapon to  destroy the freedom fighters  [Music]  i failed to save my daddy but you don't  see me crying about it every [ __ ]  second of every [ __ ] day  give me that  i don't want it anymore you can have it  back i guess